Bonowitz, Abraham J.; Papers apap186
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Abraham J. Bonowitz Papers
1977-2015
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
apap186
86.49 cubic ft.
For more than three decades, Abraham J. Bonowitz has worked to educate the public about human rights problems, in particular the death penalty and the need for alternatives to the death penalty. During this time he served in numerous director, consultant, managerial, and activist roles with leading advocacy and death penalty abolitionist organizations.
Biographical History
Abraham J. Bonowitz is a leading advocate in the abolition of the death penalty. For nearly three decades, Bonowitz has worked to educate the public about human rights problems, in particular, the death penalty and the need for alternatives to the death penalty. During this time, he served in numerous director, consultant, managerial, and activist roles with leading advocacy and death penalty abolitionist organizations. Previously, he co-founded and directed Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Penalty from 1997 to 2008, directed Floridians for Alternatives to the Death Penalty from 1999 until 2007, and served first as a consultant and then as a field manager with New Jersians for Alternatives to the Death Penalty from 2005 until 2008. Bonowitz most recently worked as director of affiliate support for the National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty. In 2004 he was elected to the board of directors of the National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty until resigning to take a staff position with the organization in 2008.
Bonowitz gained first hand knowledge of the death penalty by working in the death penalty section of the Ohio Public Defender Commission, with murder victims' family members, and with death row inmates. He appears briefly in the film "Dead Man Walking" and has worked closely on several projects with author and spiritual advisor Helen Prejean, CSJ. Bonowitz is a long-time activist with Amnesty International (AIUSA), including four years as a member of the Board of Directors of AIUSA. He is a former member of the board of directors of NCADP and also a former board member of the Journey of Hope ...From Violence to Healing, Inc., an organization led by murder victim family members.
Bonowitz is currently independently working as a campaign strategy & tactics consultant. His currents clients include the Delaware Repeal Project, the Catholic Mobilizing Network to End the Use of the Death Penalty, and Ohioans to Stop Executions. Bonowitz is deeply engaged in the strategic work of the movement.
Scope and Contents
The Abraham J. Bonowitz papers covers an expansive and prolific career as an activist and humanitarian. Bonowitz had a hand in many avenues from Amnesty International to fasting for his causes with Starvin For Justice, an annual fast and vigil to abolish the Death Penalty. Bonowitz donated extensive memorabilia from different abolitionist organizations that he was and currently active in.
The communications series encompasses mailings, newsletters, and events that Bonowitz participated in. Bonowitz corresponded with inmates as a part of his work to end the death penalty in the United States as well as improve death row conditions. He was successful in acquiring fans for all death row inmates in Florida.
As a campaign strategist, Bonowitz works with statewide organizations also seeking to end the death penalty in their state. Among the statewide abolition organizations, Bonowitz was the Director of Affiliate Support and much of his work from this period is documented in series six. Some of the prominent groups Bonowitz work with were New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalty (NJADP), Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Penalty (CUADP), Ohioans to Stop Executions, and Delaware Citizens Opposed to the Death Penalty.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is organized into the following series: Series 1: Communications; Series 2: Inmate Correspondence and Research; Series; 3: General Correspondence; Series 4: General Memorabilia; Series 5: Statewide Abolition Groups; Series 6: National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (NCADP); Series 7: Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Penalty (CUADP); Series 8: New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalty (NJADP); Series 9: Murder Victims Families for Reconciliation (MVFR) Exhibit Not in Our Name; Series 10: Subject Files; Series 11: Photographs; Series 12: Audio Visual Materials; Series 13: Amnesty International
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
All items in this collection were donated to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives, by Abraham Bonowitz in 2004, 2006, 2009, and between 20013 and 2018.
Death Penalty; Criminal Justice and Prisons; Capital punishment--United States; Death row--United States; Executions and executioners--United States; Correspondence; Newsletters; Pamphlets; Photographs; Legal documents; Bonowitz, Abraham; Pelke, Bill; Prejean, Helen; Amnesty International; Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Penalty; New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalty; Journey of Hope...from Violence to Healing; Murder Victims Families for Reconciliation; National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (U.S.)
- Communications, 1983-2013; 1; 2.6 cubic ft.
  Arrangement
  Arranged Alphabetically.
  Scope and Contents
  The communications series encompasses mailings, newsletters, and events that Mr. Bonowitz participated in.
  - Abolition Sundays Delaware Repeal Flyer, Undated (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 1)
  - Abolition Connection, 2005 February; 2005 June (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 2)
  - The Abolition of the Death Penalty in 2012: Context, Challenge and Abolitionist Strategies Activity Report (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 3)
  - Time Abolitionist, A Bi Annual Newsletter by Pennsylvanians for Alternatives to the Death Penalty, 2008 May; 2009 (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 4)
  - "Above All Else, Life" by Helen Prejean, Undated (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 5)
  - Against All Odds, Newsletter of Ohio Citizens United for Rehabilitation of Errants, 1999 November (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 6)
  - The Alligator, 2001 February; 2001 March (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 7)
  - ACLU of Florida, The Torch, 2000 February (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 8)
  - The American Catholic, 2003 November (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 9)
  - The American Prospect, A Special Report on the Death Penalty, 2004 July (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 10)
  - The American Prospect: A Special Report on the Death Penalty, 2004 July (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 11)
  - Article 3, Murder Victims' Families For Human Rights, 2005-2012 (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 12)
  - A-F Organizations Pamphlets, Undated (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 13)
  - Blind Justice, Juries Deciding Life and Death With Only Half the Truth, A Death Penalty Information Center Report, 2005 October (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 14)
  - Brethen Volunteer Service 2005 Project Book (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 15)
  - Broken Justice- The Death Penalty in Virginia, 2003 November (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 16)
  - "California Religious Groups Press Forward with Death Penalty Opposition" Death Penalty Special Report, 2001 Summer (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 17)
  - Capital Case Defense Seminar- Execution Justice Not People, 2005 February 18-21 (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 18)
  - "Capital Cases Hard For Smaller Counties" by Kate Roberts, Undated (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 19)
  - Capital Defense Handbook For Defendants and Their Families by Claudia Whitman & Lawson Strickland, 2005 (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 20)
  - Capital Punishment on the 25th Anniversary of Furman v. Georgia A Report by the Southern Center for Human Rights by Stephen B. Bright,Director, 1997 June 26 (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 21)
  - CACP News Notes, 1997-2009 (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 22)
  - The Catholic Worker, 2010 December (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 23)
  - " The Cause: A Socialist Teen Zine", 2004 January (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 24)
  - A Celebration of the Life of Rachel Carol King Memorial Program, 2008 October 12 (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 25)
  - "Choosing Mercy, Working Together to Abolish the Death Penalty" The Congregation of the Sisters of Charity of the Incarnate Word, Undated (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 26)
  - The Chronicle Philanthropy by Elizabeth Greene, 2001 March 22 (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 27)
  - Christians and Capital Punishment- Baptist General Convention of Texas Christian Life Commission, 2003 January 10 (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 28)
  - Citizens United For Rehabilitation of Errants, 2009 (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 29)
  - Civil Liberties, The American Civil Liberties Union National Newsletter, 2007; 2013 (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 30)
  - Coalition For Prisoners' Rights Newsletter, 2008 May; 2009 January (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 31)
  - Community Re-Entry Program, 1997 (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 32)
  - Compassion, Newsletter Written by Death Row Prisoners, 2004 November; 2008 January; 2008 March (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 33)
  - Creating More Victims How Executions Hurt the Families Left Behind- Murder Victims' Families for Human Rights, 2006 (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 34)
  - " A Crisis of Confindence: Americans' Doubts About the Death Penalty" A Death Penalty Information Center Report Based on a National Opinion Survey, 2007 June (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 35)
  - Dallas Peace Times, A Publication of the Dallas Peace Center, 2009 February (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 36)
  - Dead End, A No- Nonsense Resource on Capital Punishment Volume 1, Issue 1, Undated (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 37)
  - "Death Has No Appeal" European Commission Brochure, Undated (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 38)
  - " Death is Not Justice," The Council of Europe and the Death Penalty, 2001 October (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 39)
  - " The Death Penalty in Alabama: Judge Override," Equal Justice Initiative, 2011 July (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 40)
  - Death in Texas Not Even the Pretense of Fairness, 1999 July (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 41)
  - Death Penalty Defense: Tapping National Talent Seminar Program, 2004 October 22-23 (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 42)
  - Death Penalty Focus Newsletter, Undated (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 43)
  - The Death Penalty Forum- 58, 1979 (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 44)
  - Death Penalty News, Oregonians For Alternatives to the Death Penalty, 2004; 2005 (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 45)
  - "Death Penalty Opponents Rally" by Angela D. Chatman, The Plain Dealer, 2003 October 5 (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 46)
  - The Death Penalty: The Religious Community Calls For Abolition, Statements of Opposition to Capital Punishment, 2000 January (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 47)
  - Death Penalty Perform in Illinois: Five Years of Failure Annual Report- Illionois Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, 2008 (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 48)
  - Death Penalty Resources for Communities of Faith, the Death Penalty Information Center, Undated (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 49)
  - Declaration of Life, Cherish Life Circle A Sophia Circle, Undated (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 50)
  - Delaware Valley Justice Month, 2007 March (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 51)
  - El Pasoan Woman Organizes Fight Against Capital Punishment, 2000 April; 2000 May (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 52)
  - End to Capital Punishment Movement (ECPM) Newsletter, 2003 October (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 53)
  - "End to Death Penalty Urged" Central Prison March, Undated (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 54)
  - Engaging the Choir, The Kansas Campaign to Mobilize Faith Based Opposition to America's Death Penalty, 2010 November (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 55)
  - Engaging Unlikely Allies to Achieve Criminal Justice Reform- The Constitution Project, 2011 July (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 56)
  - A Pewersion of Justice by Kathryn Medico and Mollye Barrows, 2004 June (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 57)
  - "Executions, Deterrence and Homicide: A Tale of Two Cities" Working paper by Franklin E. Zimring, Jeffrey Fagan, and David T. Johnson, 2009 July 10 (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 58)
  - " Explaining Death Row's Population and Racial Composition" by John Blume, Theodore Eisenberg, and Martin T. Wells, 2004 March (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 59)
  - Families of Homicide Victims & Missing Persons, 2009 January- May (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 60)
  - Families with Loved Ones In Prison, 2001 January (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 61)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation, Undated (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 62)
  - Fla Law, University of Florida Fredric G. Levin College of Law Newsletter, 2005 February 21 (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 63)
  - The Florida Catholic, 2004 July 22 (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 64)
  - Florida Death Row Advocacy Group Newsletter, 2004 January (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 65)
  - The Florida Innocence Tour Clippings Packet, 2002 October 6- October 23 (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 66)
  - Florida Prison News, 2000 October (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 67)
  - Forsooth A Publication of the Louisville Chapter of the Fellowship of Reconciliation, 2004; 2006; 2008 (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 68)
  - Fortune News, 2000 (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 69)
  - "Free Speech Stops Here, Supreme Court Protesters Are Fined Under Inconsistently Applied Standard" by Tony Mauro, Legal Times, 1997 October 13 (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 70)
  - " Gag Order, Death- Penalty Opponent Jailed For Giving a Speech" by Dave Lindorff, In These Times, 2001 January 22 (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 71)
  - General Information Packet, Death Penalty Focus of California, 1992 April 20 (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 72)
  - "Group Travels to Speak Against Death Penalty" by Khalid Moss, Dayton Daily News, 2001 May 16 (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 73)
  - G-L Organizations Pamphlets, Undated (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 74)
  - "Hang Man The Death Penalty in Jamaica", Undated (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 75)
  - Human Beings and Human Rights Conference Materials Sponsered by California Attorneys For Criminal Justice and California Public Defenders Association [1 of 3], 2004 February 13-16 (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 76)
  - Human Beings and Human Rights Conference Materials Sponsered by California Attorneys For Criminal Justice and California Public Defenders Association [2 of 3], 2004 February 13-16 (Box 1 (1-Communications), Folder 77)
  - Human Beings and Human Rights Conference Materials Sponsered by California Attorneys For Criminal Justice and California Public Defenders Association [3 of 3], 2004 February 13-16 (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 1)
  - "I Don't Want Another Kid to Die." Families of Victims Murdered by Juvenile Oppose Juvenile Executions, 2004 (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 2)
  - I was in Prison Online Prison Ministry Newsletter, 2009 June 27 (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 3)
  - " If You Cannot Afford a Lawyer" A Report on Georgia's Failed Indigent Defense System, The Southern Center For Human Rights, 2003 January (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 4)
  - Human Rights Network News, Montana Human Rights Network, 2008 March (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 5)
  - Illegal Racial Discrimination in Jury Selection: A Continuing Legacy- Equal Justice Initiative, 2010 August (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 6)
  - "Inconsistent in Death, The Associated Press Finds Familiar Laws in the Ohio Death Penalty", 2005 May 10 (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 7)
  - Indian Report, 2007 (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 8)
  - Indiana Abolitionist, 2007 (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 9)
  - Innocence and The Crisis in the American Death Penalty- A Death Penalty Information Center Report, 2004 September (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 10)
  - Innocence and the Death Penalty: Assessing the Danger of Mistaken Executions, Staff Report by the Subcommittee on Civil and Constitutional Rights Committee on the Judiciary One Hundred Third Congress, First Session, 1993 October 21 (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 11)
  - "International Perspectives on the Death Penalty", A Report by the Death Penalty Information Center, 1999 October (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 12)
  - An Interview of A Caged Rose: Indignation of An Innocent Prisoner Unveiled Behind the Mask of Shakespeare Play Adaptations by Leon Benson, 2007 (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 13)
  - Jesus on Death Row- The Trail of Jesus and American Capital Punishment by Mark Osler, Undated (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 14)
  - "Jesus & Opinions" Chicago Jewish News, 2011 January (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 15)
  - Juan Melendez: Innocence and the Death Penalty Event Program, 2004 March 31 (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 16)
  - "Jupiter Man Crusades to end Executions" The Palm Beach Post, 2000 December 31 (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 17)
  - Just Peace- Florida's Peace & Justice Newsletter, 1998-1999; 2003; 2004; 2005 (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 18)
  - Justica, Newsletter of Judicial Process Commission, Inc., 2003 September; 2004 January (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 19)
  - Kansas Coalition Against the Death Penalty, 2009 February (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 20)
  - "Legislative Advocacy: The Nuts and Bolts of Affecting Public Policy," Jesuit Conference, 1995 January (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 21)
  - Lifelines, The Newsletter of the Tennessee Coalition to Abolish State Killing, 2006; 2007; 2010 (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 22)
  - "The Lyndhurst Sentencing Study, A Study of Patterns in Four Southern States," Published by The Southern Coalition on Jails and Prisons, Inc., 1983 (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 23)
  - " Making Your Case: Elements of A Successful Media Campaign" A Resource Developed by the Death Penalty Information Center, Undated (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 24)
  - "Mandatory Justice, Eighteen Reforms to the Death Penalty," The Constitution Project, 2001 (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 25)
  - Marin Independent Journal, 2000 November 20 (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 26)
  - "Maybe Wackenhut Languishes because of Scandalous Prisons" by Abraham Bonowitz, The Palm Beach Past, 2000 May 18 (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 27)
  - "MeVeigh Delay is Helpful to Death Penalty Critics" by Rex W.Huppke, Austin American Statesman, 2001 May 14 (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 28)
  - Millions Misspent: What Politicians Don't Say About the High Costs of the Death Penalty, A Report by the Death Penalty Information Center, 1992 October (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 29)
  - Missouri Lifeline, 2009; 2010 (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 30)
  - Moratorium News, A Publication of Equal Justice USA, 2005; 2008 (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 31)
  - M-R Organizations Pamphlet, Undated (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 32)
  - National Center For Victims of Crime National Conference, Conference Highlights, 2009 June 22-24 (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 33)
  - Newsclipping The Gator Times "Starvin' For Justice", 2001 July (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 34)
  - Newsclippings, 2000 (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 35)
  - Newsclippings, 2001 (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 36)
  - Newsclipping, 2002 (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 37)
  - Newsletter of the Parenting for Peace and Justice Network, Special Interfaith Issue, 2000 February (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 38)
  - The New Abolitionist, Newsletter of the Campaign to End the Death Penalty, 2005 May; 2006 May; 2011 Februaury; 2010 February (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 39)
  - New Hope House, Support For People on Georgia's Death Row and Their Families, 2008 December; 2010 (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 40)
  - NJ Peace Action Celebrates 50 Years of Working For Peace, 2007 May 6 (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 41)
  - NYADP News, 2004 (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 42)
  - "No to the Death Penalty" by Dale S. Recinella, The American Catholic Weekly, 2004 November 1 (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 43)
  - Not In Our Name, Murder Victims' Families Speak Out Against the Death Penalty, MVFR, Undated (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 44)
  - Not in Our Name - New Mexico, MVFR, Undated (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 45)
  - Not in Our Name North Carolina, MVFR, Undated (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 46)
  - On Wings of Hope Newsletter, 1997; 2004 January; 2005 December; 2008 January/March (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 47)
  - "An Overview of the Arguments Against the Death Penalty" by Eugene G. Wanger, Michigan Committee Against Capital Punishment, 2008 (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 48)
  - Quotes and Facts About the Death Penalty, Catholic Mobilizing Network Brochure, 2012 (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 49)
  - Raising Our Voices Newsletter, Murder Victims' Families For Reconciliation, 2007; 2011; 2012 (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 50)
  - Raising Our Voices, Tools and Techniques For Increasings the Role of Murder Victims Family Members in the Abolition Movement, 2008 (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 51)
  - People's Police Report, 2004 May; 2006 January (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 52)
  - Postcards, Undated (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 53)
  - Priests For Life Newsletter, 2004 May- June (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 54)
  - The Prison Inside the Prison: Control Units, Supermax Prisons, and Devices of Torture by Rachael Kamel and Bonnie Kerness, 2003 (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 55)
  - The Prison Payoff: The Role of Politics & Private Prisons in the Incarceration Boom by Brigette Sarabi & Edwin Bender, 2000 November (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 56)
  - PFLAG pole Newsletter, 2004 (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 57)
  - San Antonio Express News, 2001; 2002 (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 58)
  - The Santa Fe New Mexican Articles by Jane Davis, 2004 (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 59)
  - Seizing the Momentum, Texas Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty Newsletter, 2010 (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 60)
  - "Seeking Justice, Crime and Punishment in America" by William M. DiMascio, 1997 (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 61)
  - "The Sentry" The Publication of Death Penalty Focus, 1992; 2003 Winter; 2004; 2005 (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 62)
  - Signs of the Times, 2010 July (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 63)
  - Something Inside So Strong: A Resource Guide on Human Rights in the United States with Article on Death Row, 2012 July (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 64)
  - "Smart On Crime Reconsidering the Death Penalty in a Time of Economics Crisis" National Poll of Police Chiefs Put Capital Punishment at Bottom of Law Enforcement Priorities A Report by the Death Penalty Information Center, 2009 October (Box 2 (1-Communications), Folder 65)
  - Small Box: A New One Act Opera by Herman Whitfield III Program, Undated (Box 3 (1-Communications), Folder 1)
  - South Carolina Law Review- 25 years of Death: A Report of the Cornell Death Penalty Project on the "Modern" Era of Capital Punishment in South Carolina by John H. Blume, 2002 (Box 3 (1-Communications), Folder 2)
  - In Solidarity, The Newsletter of the Coalition of Arizonans to Abolish the Death Penalty, 2010 (Box 3 (1-Communications), Folder 3)
  - "Starvin' For Justice '99 Rallies Against Death Penalty" by Marianna Wertz, The New Federalist, 1999 July 12 (Box 3 (1-Communications), Folder 4)